Guide to the Time Inc. Corporate Circulation Files 1940-1987 MS 3009-RG 50
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. General Files, 1940-1987; 19 Linear feet in 19 record cartons
  - Subseries I.B. 1970 and Later, 1970-1987; 17 Linear feet in 17 record cartons
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Fall 1986 Panel 44: Control [empty] (Offsite-box 4071, Folder 17)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Fall 1986 Panel 45: Control (Offsite-box 4071, Folder 18)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Panel 1, 1986 (Offsite-box 4071, Folder 19)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Panel 2, 1986 (Offsite-box 4071, Folder 20)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Panel 3, 1986 (Offsite-box 4071, Folder 21)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Panel 4, 1986 (Offsite-box 4071, Folder 22)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Panel 5, 1986 (Offsite-box 4071, Folder 23)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Panel 6, 1986 (Offsite-box 4071, Folder 24)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Panel 7, 1986 (Offsite-box 4071, Folder 25)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Panel 8, 1986 (Offsite-box 4071, Folder 26)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Panel 9, 1986 (Offsite-box 4071, Folder 27)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Panel 10, 1986 (Offsite-box 4072, Folder 1)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Panel 12, 1986 (Offsite-box 4072, Folder 2)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Panel 13, 1986 (Offsite-box 4072, Folder 3)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Panel 14, 1986 (Offsite-box 4072, Folder 4)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Panel 15, 1986 (Offsite-box 4072, Folder 5)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Panel 16, 1986 (Offsite-box 4072, Folder 6)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Panel 19, 1986 (Offsite-box 4072, Folder 7)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Panel 20, 1986 (Offsite-box 4072, Folder 8)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Panel 42, 1986 (Offsite-box 4072, Folder 9)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Unidentified Panel, 1986 (Offsite-box 4072, Folder 10)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Unidentified Panel, 1986 (Offsite-box 4072, Folder 11)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Unidentified Panel, 1986 (Offsite-box 4072, Folder 1-13)
    - Sports Illustrated: Mailing Efforts, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 4072, Folder 14-15)
    - Sports Illustrated: Mailing Efforts, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 1)
    - Sports Illustrated: Operating Review: 1986 (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 2)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1984: Panel 34: Sweeps Format: Response Graphics (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 3)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Control [empty] (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 4)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Panel 1 [empty] (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 5)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Panel 2 [empty[ (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 6)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Panel 3 [empty] (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 7)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Panel 4 [empty] (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 8)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Panel 5 (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 9)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Panel 6 (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 10)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Panel 7 (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 11)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Panel 8 (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 12)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Panel 9, 1198586 (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 13)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Panel 10 (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 14)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Panel 11 (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 15)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Panel 12 (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 16)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Panel 13 (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 17)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Panel 14 [empty] (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 18)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Panel 15 (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 19)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Panel 18 [empty] (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 20)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Panel 19 [empty] (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 21)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Panel 20 [empty] (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 22)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Panel 21 (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 23)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Panel 22 (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 24)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Panel 23 (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 25)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Panel 24 (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 26)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Panel 25 (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 27)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Panel 26 (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 28)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Panel 27 (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 29)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Panel 28 (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 30)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Panel 29 (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 31)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Panel 30 (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 32)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Panel 32 (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 33)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Panel 33 (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 34)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Panel 34 [empty] (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 35)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Panel 35 (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 36)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Panel 36 [empty] (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 37)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Panel 37 (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 38)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Panel 38 [empty] (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 39)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Fall 1985 Panel 39 [empty] (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 40)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Panel 1: Control (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 41)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Panel 2: Offer: 2-part I.B. (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 42)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Panel 3: Term: 1 Year/6-9-24 Months (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 43)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Panel 4: Term: 7-12-24 Months (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 44)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Panel 5: Offer: 89¢/2 Years, 99¢/6-9-12 Months (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 45)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Panel 6: Price: $1.09 vs. $1.95 (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 46)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Panel 7: Price: $1.15 vs. $2.25 (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 47)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Panel 8: Package: MVP (Jack Maley/Deanna Lorenz) (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 48)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Panel 9: Premium: Walkie-Talkie (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 49)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Panel 10: Premium: AM/FM Radio (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 50)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Panel 11: Premium: Solar Calculator (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 51)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Regular Panel 12: Premium: 35mm Camera (Offsite-box 4073, Folder 52)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Regular Panel 13: Premium: Travel Alarm (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 1)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Regular Panel 14: Premium: Water Watch (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 2)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Regular Panel 15: Premium: Soundset, Member Pin (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 3)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Regular Panel 16: Premium: Watch + Compass (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 4)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Regular Panel 17: Multiple Chits (Nick Samstag/Mo Strom) (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 5)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Regular Panel 18: Package: Phone Bill (Nick Samstag/Stas' Mirek) (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 6)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Regular Panel 19: Package: Sports Adventure (Al Madden/Tom Nahigian) (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 7)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Regular Panel 20: Sweepstakes Control (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 8)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Regular Panel 21: Sweepstakes: 2C Outer on Control (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 9)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Regular Panel 22: Sweepstakes Term: 1 Year Only (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 10)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Regular Panel 23: Sweepstakes Package: Promotion (Ellen Meehling/Bob Winters) (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 11)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Regular Panel 25: Hold List 1 Year (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 12)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Regular Panel 26: Hold List Remail Voucher (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 13)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Regular Panel 27: Outside List Control (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 14)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Regular Panel 28: O/L 1 Year Term (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 15)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Regular Panel 29: O/L Remail Voucher (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 16)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Regular Panel 30: House List Continued (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 17)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Regular Panel 31: House: 6 Months (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 18)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Regular Panel 32: House: 1 Year (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 19)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Panel 33: O/L Control (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 20)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Panel 34: O/L 6 Months (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 21)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Panel 35: O/L 1 Year (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 22)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Panel 36: Premium: Binoculars (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 23)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Panel 37: Multiple Premium: Thermotag (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 24)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Control: House, Outside, Canada (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 25)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1985 Regular Control: Hold List, Time (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 26)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail July Monthly 1985 (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 27)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Panel 1: Control/Premium Tests (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 28)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Panel 2: 35mm Camera [empty] (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 29)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Panel 3: Videocassette [empty] (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 30)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Panel 4: Chronograph (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 31)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Panel 5: Football Phone (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 32)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Panel 6: Revised Time Machine (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 33)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Panel 7: Sports Watch (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 34)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Panel 8: Medallions (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 35)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Panel 9: Control National (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 36)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Panel 10: Price: 1.15/2.25 (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 37)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Panel 11: Offer: 2x I.B. (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 38)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Panel 12: Term Discount: 7 months /1.09, 12/24 months/.99 (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 39)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Panel 13: Term: 6/12/24 [empty] (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 40)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Panel 14: Term: 8/12/24 (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 41)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Panel 15: Exprn: 7 months/1 year/2 year (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 42)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Panel 16: Control: Multibuyers (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 43)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Panel 17: Multibuyer: 9/12/24 (Offsite-box 4074, Folder 44)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Panel 20: Term: 9/12/24 (Offsite-box 4075, Folder 1)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Panel 21: Term: 7/12/18/24 (Offsite-box 4075, Folder 2)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Panel 22: Issues Included vs. Free (Offsite-box 4075, Folder 3)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Panel 23: Exprn: "Like Getting Issues Free" (Offsite-box 4075, Folder 4)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Panel 24: Package: "Get the Feeling" Maley/Strom (Offsite-box 4075, Folder 5)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Panel 25: Package: "Personalized Chits" Maley/Strom (Offsite-box 4075, Folder 6)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Panel 26: Package: "Season Tickets" Singh/Flaum (Offsite-box 4075, Folder 7)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Panel 27: Package: "All-Star" Maley/Strom (Offsite-box 4075, Folder 8)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Panel 28: Premium: Swimsuit Portfolio [empty] (Offsite-box 4075, Folder 9)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Panel 29: Term: 24/12/7 (Offsite-box 4075, Folder 10)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Panel 30: Sweepstakes: "Million Dollar" Madden/Nahigian – Poly [empty] (Offsite-box 4075, Folder 11)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Panel 31: Sweepstakes: "Million Dollar" Madden/Nahigian - Kraft [empty] (Offsite-box 4075, Folder 12)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Panel 32: Offer: Cash Only for Minimum Term (Offsite-box 4075, Folder 13)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Panel 32: Frequency Test (Offsite-box 4075, Folder 14)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Test: Panel 12 (Offsite-box 4075, Folder 15)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Test: Panel 13 (Offsite-box 4075, Folder 16)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Test: Panel 16 (Offsite-box 4075, Folder 17)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Test: Panel 17 (Offsite-box 4075, Folder 18)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Test: Panel 18 (Offsite-box 4075, Folder 19)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Test: Panel 19 (Offsite-box 4075, Folder 20)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Test: Panel 21 (Offsite-box 4075, Folder 21)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Test: Panel 29 (Offsite-box 4075, Folder 22)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Test: Unidentified Panel: February 28th Reply Date (Offsite-box 4075, Folder 23)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Test: Unidentified Panel: October 1st Reply Date (Offsite-box 4076, Folder 1)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Test: Unidentified Panel: Blue Envelope, 1985 (Offsite-box 4076, Folder 2)
    - Sports Illustrated: Regular Direct Mail Spring 1986 Test: Unidentified Panel: Yellow Envelope, 1985 (Offsite-box 4076, Folder 3)
    - Sports Illustrated: Statistical History, 1954-1983 (Offsite-box 4076, Folder 4)
    - Sports Illustrated: Strategic Plan, 1985 (Offsite-box 4076, Folder 5)
    - Strategic Plan, 1983-1985 (Offsite-box 4076, Folder 6)
    - Strategic Plan Review 10/84, 1984 (Offsite-box 4076, Folder 7)
    - Strategic Research Plans 1986, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 4076, Folder 8)
    - Subscription Data, undated (Offsite-box 4076, Folder 9)
    - Subscription Data: Canada, 1972 (Offsite-box 4076, Folder 10)
    - Subscription Data: Terms and Rates, undated (Offsite-box 4076, Folder 11)
    - Time, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 4076, Folder 12)
    - Time (Problem), 1985 (Offsite-box 4076, Folder 13-15)
    - Time (Problem) [Restricted], 1985 (Offsite-box R86)
    - Time Telephone Marketing (TTM) (Continued) [2/2] [1985-1986] Videos (Offsite-box 4076, Folder 16)
    - Time Telephone Marketing (TTM) (Continued] [Restricted], 1985 (Offsite-box R86)
    - View, 1973 (Offsite-box 4076, Folder 17)
    - View 2/15/72 VA Jayme - Johnson - 1 year/$7, 1972 (Offsite-box 4077, Folder 1)
    - View 2/15/72 VB Jayme - Johnson - 1 year/$9, 1972 (Offsite-box 4077, Folder 2)
    - View 2/15/72 VE Jayme - Johnson - $15/year, 1972 (Offsite-box 4077, Folder 3)
    - View 2/15/72 VF Jayme - Johnson Advance Proofs - 1 year/$12, 1972 (Offsite-box 4077, Folder 4)
    - View 2/15/72 VT Jayme- 1 year/$12, 1972 (Offsite-box 4077, Folder 5)
    - View Direct Mail Test VT - Jayme Letter (No Brochure) Mail Date: 2/15/72 - $12/year, 1972 (Offsite-box 4077, Folder 6)
    - View Plans, 1972 (Offsite-box 4077, Folder 7)
    - View VA – 200 Jayme-Johnson - $17/year 2/15/72, 1972 (Offsite-box 4077, Folder 8)
    - View VC 202 Jayme-Johnson Brochure - $12/year 2/15/72, 1972 (Offsite-box 4077, Folder 9)
    - Weekly Magazine Group Reports, 1986 (Offsite-box 4077, Folder 10-11)
    - Well, 1972-1974 (Offsite-box 4078, Folder 1)
    - Well Plans, 1972 (Offsite-box 4078, Folder 2)
    - Well 2/17/72 - COA - Jayme (No Brochure) - 1 year/$9, 1972 (Offsite-box 4078, Folder 3)
    - Well 2/17/72 COB Jayme – 1 year/$12, 1972 (Offsite-box 4078, Folder 4)
    - Well 2/17/72 – COC – Jayme – 1 year/$15, 1972 (Offsite-box 4078, Folder 6)
    - Well – Direct Mail Retest - Washington (WA) 1 Jayme Letter Only (TI) - Mail Date: 2/17/72 - 1 year/$12, 1972 (Offsite-box 4078, Folder 7)
    - Well – Fall '71 Direct Mail Test - RAF Rainbow - $1/month quarterly - 9/30/72, 1972 (Offsite-box 4078, Folder 8)
    - Well – Fall '71 Direct Mail Test – RAF Rainbow - $5/6 months - 9/30/71, 1971 (Offsite-box 4078, Folder 9)
    - Well: Test Material from Irene Sullivan, 1972 (Offsite-box 4078, Folder 10)
    - Worldwide Publications (1), 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 4078, Folder 11)
    - Worldwide Publications (2), 1979-1985 (Offsite-box 4078, Folder 12-13)
    - You, 1986 (Offsite-box 4078, Folder 14)
- Series II. International Distribution Files, 1945-1967; 1.5 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
  International Distribution Files consists of correspondence and agreements with foreign entities to market and sell Time Inc. magazines in foreign territories not directly served by Time Inc. itself.
  - Agencia de Publicaciones (Nicaragua) [Restricted], 1952 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Agencias Steer, S.A. (Panama) [Restricted], 1953 (Offsite-box R86)
  - A.G.I.R.E (Rome), 1946-1947, 1953 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 1)
  - A.G.I.R.E (Rome) [Restricted], 1946 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Agencia de Publicaciones Selecta (Honduras), 1951-1952 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 2)
  - Agencia Franco-Uruguaya de Distribucion - Paraguay, 1952, 1953 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 3)
  - Agencias Steer, S.A. (Panama), 1950-1953 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 4)
  - American Magazine Distributors, Inc. (T.L. Chow), 1947-1951, 1954, 1956 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 5)
  - American Magazine Distributors, Inc. (T.L. Chow) [Restricted], 1947 (Offsite-box R86)
  - American News Co. - New York City, 1947, 1949, 1952 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 6)
  - Amerind Co. - Calcutta, India and American-Indian Co. - New York City, 1947 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 7)
  - The Argosy Company Ltd. Georgetown British Guiana [Restricted], 1955, 1961 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Army Times - Washington, D.C., 1950-1952 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 8)
  - Army Times - Washington, D.C. [Restricted], 1950-1952 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Aruba Boekhandel Aruba, Netherlands Antilles (N.A.) [Restricted], 1955 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Ashrsh Brother, Bahrain Persian Gulf, 1953 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 9)
  - Associated Distributors. Ltd. - Colombo, Ceylon, 1947-1948 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 10)
  - Atilio Cardellino - Asuncion, Paraguay, 1953-1954 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 11)
  - Atilio Cardellino - Asuncion, Paraguay [Restricted], 1953 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Azed, A.G. [Restricted] 1947-[Restricted], 1948 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Beverhoudt & Co., Ltd. - Canal Zone, 1953, 1955 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 12)
  - Bofan Publications Inc. Miami Florida [Restricted], 1961 (Offsite-box R86)
  - The Bookshop (Saigon, Viet-Nam) [Restricted], 1964 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Bokeverzlun Sigfuser Eymunissonar (Ey.) Iceland, 1953 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 13)
  - Butler's Inc. Agana, Guam, 1947-1950, 1954 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 14)
  - Butler's Inc. Agana, Guam [Restricted], 1947-1950, 1954 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Cadenas Moreno, Leopoldo J. - Havana, Cuba, 1954 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 15)
  - Cadenas Moreno, Leopoldo J. - Havana, Cuba [Restricted], 1955 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Caja de Auxilio de Venedores de Diarios y Revistas Montevideo, Uruguay, 1955, 1961 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 16)
  - Caja de Auxilio de Venedores de Diarios y Revistas Montevideo, Uruguay [Restricted], 1955 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Cano Isaza & CIA Bogata, Colombia (El Espectador) [Restricted], 1963 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Cardenas, A. - Bucaramanga, Colombia, 1953 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 17)
  - Cardenas, A. - Bucaramanga, Colombia [Restricted], 1948, 1953 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Casa América Moreno Hermanoes (Hnos.) Paraguay [Restricted], 1957 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Castro Marquez, J. - Bogota Colombia [Restricted], 1949, 1951 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Clarac, Paul Journaux Librarie-Papeterie Fort de France, Martinique, 1948, 1951 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 18)
  - Consolidated Press Ltd. Sydney, Australia, 1950-1951, 1954, 1956 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 19)
  - Consolidated Press Ltd. Sydney, Australia [Restricted], 1951 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Continental Druckschriften (Conwa) Germany, 1950, 1952-1955 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 20)
  - Continental Druckschriften (Conwa) Germany [Restricted], 1950, 1953 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Conwa Grossovertrieb [Restricted], 1963 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Cooper, Reginald Paget, Bermuda [Restricted], 1949 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Costandia, Co. - Dr. A.M. Quesada - Lima, Peru, 1952 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 21)
  - Costandia, Co. - Dr. A.M. Quesada - Lima, Peru [Restricted], 1954 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Distribuidora Colombiana - Cali, Valle, Comlombia 1966 [Restricted] (Offsite-box R86)
  - Distribuidora Colombiana de Publicaciones Cali, Colombia, 1951-1953 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 22)
  - Distribuidora Colombiana de Publicaciones Cali, Colombia [Restricted], 1951-1953 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Distribuidor Santiago C.A. Caracas Venezuela, 1950-1953 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 23)
  - Distribuidor Santiago C.A. Caracas Venezuela [Restricted], 1966 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Domican Gift Shop Ciudad, Trujillo Domican Republic, 1952-1953 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 24)
  - Domican Gift Shop Ciudad, Trujillo Domican Republic [Restricted], 1953 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Droguett & CIA - Chile, 1955 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 25)